Is an early something that looks like this but it's long version
看起来像这样的早期版本，但它是长版本
Zucchini pizza Crazy
西葫芦比萨疯狂
Cucumber with chicken
鸡肉黄瓜
Pure kiwi ok
纯奇异果好
Anything about the best way the movie
关于电影的最佳方式
I did not know this is a kiwi I thought you told me it was a human
我不知道这是猕猴桃我以为你告诉我那是人类
Yeah I have no idea how to peel a kiwi
是的，我不知道怎么去皮
This may or may not work like ginger
这可能像姜一样起作用或可能不起作用
It is not
它不是
Turn the radio off
关闭收音机
I understand that you don't need it with the hair on it but they're here
我知道您不需要头发，但他们在这里
Is there an Ashley very fast carpet from the sun
有没有阿什利晒得很快的地毯
I'll just be rated laboriously with an interesting
我会很努力地给我打分
Oh that's Green
哦，那是绿色的
First start with this pillar
首先从这个支柱开始
Inexpensive cures for thanks but pretty much everything if you just take a sharp knife down the side of it
便宜的治疗方法，谢谢，但是如果您用锋利的刀沿它的侧面削去几乎所有的东西
The skinwalker mouth
皮肤行者的嘴
I'm feeling it like upside down
我感觉像颠倒了
H&M around the edge
H＆M边缘化
Suggest take the skin right off
建议马上脱皮
NewsNow Liverpool
Life hacks
生活技巧
Do you need a night
你需要一个晚上吗
Disney On Ice
迪士尼冰上舞会
She's peeled
她去皮了
How many weird
多少怪异
Skinless now
现在无皮
We're going to kill this Kiwi I like
我们要杀死这个我喜欢的猕猴桃
A nice clean kiwi
干净的奇异果
It's just not fair
只是不公平
Can I cut the ends off
我可以切断两端吗
I'm just going to play with
我只是要玩
I find that I get the best results like this just because I have a lot more control this takes a little bit of Technique but
我发现获得这样的最佳效果只是因为我拥有更多的控制权，这需要一些技巧，但是
You get a nice shaped kiwi from
你会得到一个漂亮的异型猕猴桃
Ok all the skin is off
好吧，所有的皮肤都脱落了
Kiwi
奇异果
Another way to cut the ends off first It just gives you a better place to start
另一种切断末端的方法只是为您提供了一个更好的起点
Give me sharp Taylor
给我敏锐的泰勒
Radio hand
收音机手
Mpo last nice and smooth
MPO最后不错
If at the end it's all slipping you can hold it you can always put into a paper towel
如果最后都滑了，可以握住它，可以随时放入纸巾中
So does a cicada have
蝉也有
And that's another way to peel a kiwi
这是剥猕猴桃的另一种方法
First one is a sport
第一个是一项运动
Still need my paring knife I've got to cut the ends off and then I'm going to do something to get my spoon and logic
仍然需要我的削皮刀，我必须剪掉两端，然后我要做一些事情来弄我的汤匙和逻辑
The skin
皮
And the kiwi
和猕猴桃
Canape lit around in the skin pretty much as possible
烤面包片尽可能多地在皮肤周围点亮
And they go from the other end
他们从另一端走
Don't worry if the skin breaks are not really going to save it
不用担心皮肤破裂是否真的可以保存它
Anarchy we can dislike
我们可能不喜欢的无政府状态
Shoot out the
射出
30p lucky movie
30p幸运电影
And one of the ways to cut this is the country
减少这种情况的方法之一就是国家
Always just like a hot dog
总是像热狗一样
Can you get a cup with a thin Rim and you can enlarge it in there
你能得到一个带有薄轮辋的杯子吗？
And just put it onto the rim of the cup where is this is a bit of a waste if you don't have a really
只是将它放在杯子的边缘，如果您没有
And that was a few ways to peel a kiwi
那是剥猕猴桃的几种方法